Where is this treasure month? This is obviously a fake Zangetsu! Super fake Tibetan doll, Asara treasure!
Have you noticed that the treasures produced during this treasure month are extremely fake?
And it is a fake appearance. No matter what kind of treasure,
The value of its treasure body is several times lower than the items it opens, and the higher the quality of the treasure, the
The gap is getting bigger. For high-quality treasures, you need to go to Jimmy Dam to get them.
The treasures produced by Jimmy Dam are one level higher than ordinary dams.
It is recommended that you run more and put it in the warehouse.
This is equivalent to hiding energy behind the warehouse value without increasing it.
Normally, it won't take up too much of your warehouse value.
When you go bankrupt, you can draw out a lot of cash.
And the planner very naturally included the treasure map into the account losses.
After the treasure map brought in from outside the bureau is consumed, it will be included in the bureau's losses.
I am really afraid that you will get false accounts during the treasure activity.